[
    {
        "question": "The total assets of the debit account v/suppliers express:",
        "answers": [
            "a) The cost for purchases made",
            "b) Payments made",
            "c) The amount of invoices to be paid",
            "d) The amount of invoices to be received"
        ],
        "right_answer": 3,
        "hints": [
            "A debt is a sum of money that you have to pay at the end of the predetermined deadline"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The credits of the V/Customer credit account expresses the total amount:",
        "answers": [
            "a) Of invoices issued",
            "b) Of  sales revenues",
            "c) Of invoice still to be collected",
            "d) Of invoices to be paid "
        ],
        "right_answer": 3,
        "hints": [
            "The credit is a sum of money that the creditor must collect by he end of the predetermined deadline"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is deindustrialization?",
        "answers": [
            "a) It is the process of decrease in the importance of service and industry in",
            "b) The economy and the increase in the importance of the tertiary sector in",
            "c) The production;",
            "d) It is a term that refers to the move away from the primary sector to the secondary sector;",
            "e) Is the process of decrease in the importance of industry and manufacturing in the economy and the increase in the importance in the tertiary sector of production;",
            "f) Is the process that is influencing the developing countries."
        ],
        "right_answer": 3,
        "hints": [
            "the deindustralisation is the move away from the industralisation to the service sector"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is microcredit?",
        "answers": [
            "a) Is the extension of big amount of money to unemployed people and others that lives in poverty;",
            "b) Is the extension of microloans to people who find impossible to obtain a loan because they don't meet any of the traditional requirements for credit and lives in poverty; ",
            "c) Is the extension of microloans to people that meet traditional requiments for credit;",
            "d) Is the extension small amount of money to people that find impossible to have a loans because they meet traditional requiments for credit;"
        ],
        "right_answer": 2,
        "hints": [
            "a traditional requiments for credits are for example: collateral and employment."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "an enterprises is:",
        "answers": [
            "a) A series of right connected between them for a personal purpose;",
            "b) Is an economic activity organized for the purpose of production or the exchange of goods and service;",
            "c) An activity that fulfill series of deeds that aren\u2019t connected between them;",
            "d) Is an activity that cannot have more than one entrepreneur;"
        ],
        "right_answer": 2,
        "hints": [
            "enterprices is aimed at achieving an economic purpose, of both public and private interest"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The commercial brand:",
        "answers": [
            "a) Replaces the manufacturer\u2019s one;",
            "b) Identifies the manufacturer\u2019s one;",
            "c) An be placed next to the manufacturer\u2019s one;",
            "d) Doesn't identify the reseller\u2019s one."
        ],
        "right_answer": 3,
        "hints": [
            "it cannot hide or replace the manufacturer\u2019s one."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The functional distribution measures the income received:",
        "answers": [
            "a) From various production sectors;",
            "b) From various social classes;",
            "c) From various subjects;",
            "d) From the various factors of production;"
        ],
        "right_answer": 4,
        "hints": [
            "it analyzes the distribution of RN between wages, profits, rents and interests directed at specific people."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Owners receive the differential annuity on the basis of:",
        "answers": [
            "a) Soil fertility;",
            "b) The location of the soil;",
            "c) The actual performance of the soil;",
            "d) To the resources of the subsoil;"
        ],
        "right_answer": 1,
        "hints": [
            "david riccardo saw that all soils have different productivity so he theorized the law of diminishing returns"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "An\u00a0interpretation\u00a0key\u00a0is\u00a0required\u00a0to\u00a0obtain\u00a0information",
        "answers": [
            "a) True",
            "b) False"
        ],
        "right_answer": 0,
        "hints": [
            "to arrive at the information the data must be analyzed."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Redundancy is the repetition of data",
        "answers": [
            "a) True",
            "b) False"
        ],
        "right_answer": 0,
        "hints": [
            "\nredundancy happened before the database was introduced, so before that happened most data was stored more than once."
        ]
    }
]